KUMHAR KULDEEP KANAIYALAL

Fullstack Developer

CONTACT

7627096127

kuldeepkumhar100@gmail.com https://www.hackerearth.com/@k

umhar

EDUCATION

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Maharishi arvind institute of engineering and technology, mansarowar - jaipur, rajasthan 302020 (B.Tech Computer Science 76%)

2017-2021

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Radhakrishana Vidyalaya Bicholim -Goa 403503 (12th class 62%)

2010 - 2016

SKILLS

C, C++, Javascript, Python, Nodejs, Database, Linux, AWS, JIRA, GitHub,

REFERENCES

Provided upon request.

SUMMARY

Experienced and dedicated full stack mobile app developer offering more than 3 years of expertise to the IT industry. Dynamic and personable with strong focus on application lifecycle. Strengths in cross-platform mobile development with React Native.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (REACT NATIVE + NODEJS)

Dev Technosys Pvt. Ltd., Jaipur -Rajasthan

2022 - Present

- Designed Database schema for an e-commerce application.
- Developed REST APIs with efficient response time.
- Integrated firebase push notifications from Backend for mobile.
- Used AWS service architecture for maintaining media files. applications.
- Responsible for creating the custom Push Developed front end functionality. including RESTful service

REACT NATIVE DEVELOER

BR Software, Pvt. Ltd, Jaipur-Rajasthan

2020-2021

- Developed front end functionality. including RESTful service.
- Integrated the payment gateway services like razorpay, cashfree, deep linking, microsoft appearer codepush,
- Made app live on both app store and play store.
- Customized the push notification service.
- Used redux, saga for code and performance betterment.

REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER

Fulminous Software Pvt. Ltd

2019-2020

- Designed the responsive UI for the applications like e-commercee, cab booking and etc.
- Used core components of the react native and contributed in responsice UI.
- Integrated the packages line image picker, calender, etc.

PROJECT LINKS





